

export const AllQuestions = [
    {
        id: 1,
        hint: "Capital of India",
        question: "_E_H_",
        answer: "dli",
        isAnswered: false
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        hint: "Round breakfast food with holes",
        question: "_A_E_",
        answer: "bgl",
        isAnswered: false
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        hint: "Yellow fruit loved by monkeys",
        question: "_A_A_A",
        answer: "bnn",
        isAnswered: false
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        hint: "Full of keys but can not open doors",
        question: "_I_N_",
        answer: "pao",
        isAnswered: false
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        hint: "Has a face and two hands but no arms or legs",
        question: "C_O_K",
        answer: "lc",
        isAnswered: false
    },
    {
        id: 6,
        hint: "Cold, white, and falls from the sky",
        question: "S_O_",
        answer: "nw",
        isAnswered: false
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        hint: "Can fly without wings",
        question: "K_T_",
        answer: "ie",
        isAnswered: false
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        hint: "Something you read, with pages and words",
        question: "B_O_",
        answer: "ok",
        isAnswered: false
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        hint: "A building where you learn things",
        question: "S_H_O_",
        answer: "col",
        isAnswered: false
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        hint: "Something you wear on your feet to keep them warm",
        question: "S_C_S",
        answer: "ok",
        isAnswered: false
    },
    {
        id: 11,
        hint: "A place where you can swim, but not the sea",
        question: "P_O_",
        answer: "ol",
        isAnswered: false
    }
    
]

